[{"answer": "You'll reap the benefits, but are you truly prepared to be despised within the department", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "So be it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "They stick you with a name like my friend, you look for an alias", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'm sorta between jobs.  Look, what do you say we, uh..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Sir, I took the call.  It's my case", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes, I do, sir", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah I know.  my friend's running whores and judging by his address, probably something bigger on the side.  He doesn't want any attention", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why was my friend at the Nite Owl", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You look better than my friend.  Now, ", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "He had you cut to look like my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I never truck with no sissies", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Believed what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.  That was a long time ago.  Before your day.  The last few years he's been muscle for hire.  But I heard he's disappeared", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "More's gonna cost you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Before my friend disappeared he was popping off about trying to move eighteen pounds of heroin", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend.  my friend's narcotics lieutenant.  The night he got clipped, eighteen pounds of my friend's heroin went missing", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Why do men and women usually see each other", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Then try talking to my lawyer. Good evening, gentlemen", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Tell him Sergeant that place is coming in to talk to him", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'm going to my friend's.  I'll meet you at the Dining Car", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What's this all about, lad", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You're Narco, lad, not Homicide. And since when do you work with my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Without what, his smearing yours first?  What's he got on you, my friend?  Pictures of you and an out of work actor with your pants down", "docId": "ellay-confidential_early.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The proof had his throat slit.  So far you're not denying it", "qsentId": 26}]